Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™
Modify by Blue-Bird™
(https://subscene.com/u/1191276)
♪ I've been watchin' you for some time ♪
♪ Can't stop starin' at those ocean eyes ♪
KCRW,
and worldwide at KCRW.com.
It's Billie Eilish and her "Ocean Eyes."
♪ Can't stop staring at... ♪
You guys are on the radio
on KCRW, the coolest radio ever.
♪ I've never fallen from quite this high ♪
-♪ Fallin' into your ocean eyes ♪
-Yeah.
♪ Those ocean eyes ♪
That's Billie!
Billie. I couldn't get any tickets
for your concert, but I'm here.
Billie!
-I love you so much.
-Thank you.
Careful with her.
-I love you.
-I love you, Billie!
Billie, I love you!
♪ Aah ♪
♪ The games you played were never fun ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ You'd say you'd stay
But then you'd run ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ Giving you what you're begging for
Giving you what you say I need ♪
♪ I don't want any settled scores
I just want you to set me free ♪
♪ Giving you what you're begging for
Giving you what you say I need ♪
♪ Say I need ♪
♪ I'm not afraid anymore ♪
♪ What makes you sure ♪
♪ You're all I need? ♪
♪ Forget about it ♪
♪ When you walk out the door
And leave me torn ♪
♪ You're teaching me to live without it ♪
♪ Bored ♪
♪ I'm so bored ♪
♪ So bored ♪
♪ I'm home alone
You're God-knows-where ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ I hope you don't think
That shit's fair ♪
♪ Giving you all you want and more ♪
♪ Giving you every piece of me ♪
♪ I don't want love I can't afford ♪
♪ I just want you to love for free ♪
♪ Can't you see that I'm getting bored? ♪
-♪ Giving you ♪
-♪ Every piece of me ♪
♪ Piece of me ♪
♪ I'm not afraid anymore ♪
♪ What makes you sure you're all I need? ♪
♪ Forget about it ♪
♪ When you walk out the door ♪
♪ And leave me torn ♪
♪ You're teaching me ♪
♪ I'm so bored ♪
♪ Say I need ♪
♪ Settled scores
Set me free ♪
♪ Begging for ♪
♪ Say I need ♪
♪ I'm not afraid anymore ♪
♪ What makes you sure ♪
♪ You're all I need? ♪
♪ Forget about it ♪
♪ When you walk out the door
And leave me torn ♪
♪ You're teaching me to live without it ♪
You guys are all so beautiful.
Someone's hurt.
-Someone-- Hey, hey, hey.
-Someone's hurt.
-Someone's turnt.
Guys, make room. Make room.
-Billie!
That's my sister!
Okay, she's okay. She's okay.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah!
Hey, you guys need to be fucking okay,
'cause y'all are the reason I'm okay,
okay?
I'd look into the crowd
and I see all these faces.
So many different feelings and heartbreak.
And every single person in there,
you know, is going through something good
or bad, or horrible or amazing, you know?
And the least I can do is...
make art that I make
because I have the same problems.
I don't think of them as fans... ever.
They're not my fans.
They're, like, part of me.
My family's the reason I'm the way I am.
You played a duet. Your first duet.
-What?
-A duet.
For some people, it's where they grow up
that made them who they are.
Where they went to school,
who they hung out with.
And for me, it was completely my mom
and my dad and my brother and my dog.
My mom taught me how to write songs.
My dad taught me how to play the piano
and the ukulele.
And I would do, like, talent shows
when I was little,
and my dad would play ukulele for me
or my mom would play guitar.
My brother would sing harmony.
It was always like that.
Our family was just one big fucking song.
And I still make music
in my brother's bedroom.
♪ Said out loud ♪
-Nice.
-♪ Said out loud ♪
-That sounds good.
-Go. Go.
♪ Come here ♪
♪ Probably something that shouldn't be ♪
♪ Said out loud ♪
♪ Honestly, I thought that I would be ♪
♪ Dead by now ♪
♪ Probably something
That shouldn't be... ♪
♪ I wanna end me ♪
Whoo! That's dope.
♪ What do you want from me? ♪
♪ Why don't you run from me? ♪
♪ What are you wondering? ♪
-♪ What do you know? ♪
-Whoo!
-♪ Why aren't you scared of me? ♪
-I'm so proud of that one.
♪ Why do you care for me? ♪
♪ When we all fall asleep
Where do we go? ♪
-That's cool, right?
-Genius.
This is what I want the album
to be called.
"When We All Fall Asleep,
Where Do We Go?"
I actually drew this song.
This is the drawing of this song
'cause the whole song is about, like,
monsters under your bed.
In the future,
I'm gonna do stuff with wings.
And I also wanna do something
where I drink black liquid
and then my eyes turn black, and then
I start bleeding black out of my eyes.
This is a self-portrait.
This is some dick, some weird doll.
This is a foot.
There's some drips,
and you can decide whatever the drips are.
There's some bitch.
There's a hairy vagina.
There, a-- a dick.
-♪ ...'cause I don't know ♪
-Ooh, that's cool.
♪ I can't say no ♪
-♪ I can't say no ♪
♪ Boom, step on the glass ♪
♪ Staple your tongue ♪
-♪ Aah ♪
What can we-- Can we wrap it
back into the bad dream thing?
-Just something to wrap that all in.
-What if it's, like, sleep paralysis?
♪ My limbs all froze
And can't feel my toes ♪
"Can't feel my toes" is not cool enough.
-No, it's not.
-But, like--
My limbs all froze...
and my eyes won't close.
That's actually cool.
Your-- You think "my eyes won't"
or "my eyes can't"? Like--
"Won't" is way cooler.
Okay.
♪ The debt I owe, gotta sell my soul ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't say no
No, I can't say no ♪
♪ My limbs all froze
And my eyes won't close ♪
♪ I can't say no, I can't say no ♪
♪ Step on the glass ♪
♪ Staple your tongue, aah ♪
Bop! Bop!
Keep going.
Wait. No, no.
No, no, no.
Actually, let's just do that--
Let's do that, like, 17 times.
So this is not the first shot,
but this is the angle that I want
once it zooms out--
-is not fully to the side.
-What are you doing right now?
Shut up!
And not to the front,
-just, like... so that that...
-Pepper, uh-uh.
...the chair leg,
that's, like, in the middle.
-So I want it to start...
-Where's that cat?
...with nothing in the background--
-Give her a gold star.
-With nothing in the background
except...
...except the white cyc
-and the white table.
-Oh, yeah.
There's a dead rat over there.
So this is the first shot
of just the glass.
Zooms out,
keeping the glass in the center,
and I'm looking at the glass.
Once it gets to this point,
then I will take a drink.
Start drinking it.
I don't know if I want it to stay here
while I drink it until I put it down
and then come up to me,
or if while I'm drinking it--
Wait, keep drinking it.
I don't know yet if I want it.
'Cause I don't know if I...
or-- want it to stay diagonal.
'Cause I don't know if I want it to...
What the fuck am I saying?
I don't know if I want to see...
Here's-- Okay, wait. I've decided.
It's gonna be here.
Once I start drinking,
and I've been drinking for a second,
it's gonna come, stay with this leg
exactly even in the middle
and exactly even to the leg
the opposite way.
Come so that my face is in the middle.
I think I'll probably grab the glass
with my left hand
so that the shot is-- make--
Thank you, Mom.
...makes more sense.
And then you'll see that
the black goo is disappearing
'cause I'm drinking all of it.
Then put it down.
And then I'm just gonna look
into the camera,
and then it'll stay exactly there.
Don't zoom!
Don't do anything like
these bozo fucking filmmakers do
when they try to have it not be boring.
-You are working with a great director.
-Shut the fuck up.
-He'll have genius.
-Okay, I'm sure, but I--
I'm telling you don't be an idiot.
-Stay here.
-Billie.
And don't move the stupid camera,
and then as I look into the camera,
the black will drip from me eyes.
Okay, same deal.
How's that one feel?
-It's pretty good.
-Pretty good?
You're a fucking trouper
for agreeing to this.
It is my idea.
Some things can't be unseen.
Is that one yours or mine?
-I can't...
-Push.
-This makes my Tourette's insane.
-I say we go for it.
'Cause it's, like, in my eye
where my Tourette's live.
This one's mine.
All right, ready?
-And...
-Can you look up just a bit?
-There it is.
Here we go.
Oh, put it down. Slowly.
Go.
Let's go again. All right, cut, cut, cut.
Reset it. We'll try it again.
Cut. Cut, cut, cut, cut.
Cameras rolling.
I don't know
what the fuck I'm supposed to do.
Keep an eye for when
you're setting the glass down,
-'cause I think we lost your hand a bit--
-Do what?
When you drop it, after you drink it,
and you're placing it back on the thing,
just look at the motion of the camera,
'cause I think you might have to make it
a little slower.
Yeah, I don't know
when I'm supposed to do that.
So if you could shout it out
that would be great.
You want me to say, like, "Glass down"?
-Yeah.
-"Down," or something like that?
Or "Start bringing the glass down,"
and I'll just do it slower.
Okay. Cool.
Oh, that's great.
Cut. Yeah.
For the next, rest of the videos,
I'm directing them all myself.
What?
Record this.
Record this. Oh.
Oh, my God.
We have to have
the first track of the album just be that.
All right. I've taken my teeth out.
Let's make an album.
I've taken my teeth out.
My Invisalign has...
-I have taken out my Invisalign...
-I have taken out my Invisalign.
...and this is the album.
♪ White shirt now red, my bloody nose ♪
-♪ Sleepin', you're on your tippy-toes ♪
-♪ Creepin' around like no one knows ♪
-♪ Creepin' ♪
♪ My little criminal ♪
Or, like...
What if it's like:
♪ Think you're such a criminal ♪
Like he thinks he's bad,
and he's not even.
We could even-- I don't know about this,
but I just remembered that song "bad guy."
This could be that song.
I'm just saying, like--
I'm just coming up with random things.
It could be like,
"You think you're such a bad guy,"
and then the hook thing could be, like,
"But I'm the bad guy."
Right? I don't know
if that's right for this one.
I like that.
"Blocking an intersection during
rush hour traffic is not permitted:
unless you entered the intersection
on a green light.
Under any circumstances
even if your light is green.
Unless you have
the right-of-way or green light"--
-It's under any--
-I tuned out on that one.
Under any circumstances.
Because you can't-- If you--
If there's traffic and it's stopped,
you can't enter the intersection.
That blocks everything. That's illegal.
"Under"-- Yeah, so no.
It's called don't block the box.
Yes. Correct.
That's what they say in New York.
Don't block the box.
That's about a vagina.
Billie passed her permit test.
Look at that.
Billie passed her test.
She can drive now.
Well, she can take lessons.
I've always wanted to drive.
I just, like, love cars.
Of course, my mom has a van,
and my dad has a fucking Mazda.
And Finneas has a Honda Fit,
so I'm just, like, drowning in losers.
Oh, my gosh.
All I want is
a matte black Dodge Challenger.
♪ Won't let you take it back
And only if you say... ♪
Wish I couldn't hear you
saying that, or...
♪ Don't do any... ♪
♪ Say you were... ♪
-Dope.
-♪ You didn't mean to say it ♪
♪ Don't do any--
Don't you think-- ♪
♪ Won't you come and take it back? ♪
♪ Maybe won't you take it back? ♪
♪ Say you were trying to make me laugh ♪
♪ And nothin' has to change today ♪
♪ You didn't mean to say I love you ♪
♪ And I love you ♪
Some crazy harmonies on the oo's, right?
Already have 'em.
-♪ I can love you ♪
-♪ I love you ♪
Like, half-note harmonies. Sick.
-Oh, yeah.
-Beautiful.
It's so pretty.
It reminds me of that wonderful
Duncan Sheik song that we loved so well...
-There we go. There it is.
-...but a completely different song.
-So beautiful.
-No, it has this incredible--
People who don't write songs are always
reminded of songs from other songs.
No, it's not like it
sounds like something.
He's just saying
it gives him the same beautiful feeling.
Thanks.
-Beautiful.
-That was great.
-That was fun to write.
-It's a good start.
-Love that.
-Yeah.
♪ Don't ask questions
You don't wanna know ♪
♪ Learned my lesson way too long ago ♪
♪ To be talkin' to you, belladonna ♪
♪ Should've taken a break
Not an Oxford comma ♪
♪ Take what I want when I wanna ♪
♪ And I want ya ♪
♪ Bad, bad news
One of us is gonna lose ♪
♪ I'm the powder, you're the fuse ♪
♪ Just add some friction ♪
♪ You are my strange addiction ♪
♪ Doctor can't explain
My symptoms or my pain ♪
♪ But you are my strange addiction ♪
It's a corny beat, but--
It's kinda cute though.
I think we should try to finish a song,
and go, like--
Give us notes, give us feedback.
Let's get this one done.
-Got it.
-And then
still keep circling around
with other stuff.
Don't focus exclusively on anything,
just whatever you guys want.
If they're all moving towards something...
I like what Justin was saying though.
What'd you say?
-What?
-I like what Justin's saying.
-What's Justin saying?
-No pressure.
-No pressure?
-Yeah, of course.
There really is no pressure.
All I'm saying is
that if we wanna put anything out,
we should just finish whatever that is.
If that's "Crown," we'll put that out.
-You know-- Do you hear that at all?
-Yep.
If we focus on something,
we can finish it, as opposed to, like,
doing a little bit of it
and jumping to another thing,
and doing a bit of it
and jumping to another thing.
That's all I'm saying.
So "7," "i love you"
and we have to finish
"all the good girls go to hell."
It's actually so close,
you know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-Once we get the things right--
"My strange addiction"
is sounding, uh, good!
I feel like if I heard that, I'd be like,
"This is gonna be a hit," you know?
Absolutely.
Somebody was thinking that
in that meeting.
-I think everyone was thinking that.
-Why didn't they say anything?
Why didn't they clap?
♪ All the good girls ♪
♪ All the good girls go to hell ♪
♪ 'Cause even God herself has enemies ♪
♪ And once the water starts to rise ♪
♪ And heaven's out of sight ♪
♪ She'll want the devil on her team ♪
-Sounds great.
-Sounds pretty horrible.
I think it sounds kinda awesome.
It's pretty bad.
I hate that
we have to have this album done
by December.
The day before my birthday. I hate that.
We have to have it mastered
the day before your birthday.
-We'll have it done weeks before that.
-No, we won't.
-Yeah.
We said we'd have it done
before this tour.
Well, we have a deadline now,
and we have an album release,
so we'll have it done.
But we won't have it done if we don't
do it, so that's why we're doing it.
But it sounds bad!
And I sound horrible, and I can't
sound good 'cause I'm not good.
-You're very good.
-No, I'm not.
Lots of people would agree with me
that you're very good.
We need to finish the four more.
If we go, "Clear our schedule of
everything except shows until the 17th."
If we get all that done,
and we send it to Riback,
and Riback's like,
"I don't hear a hit on this record,"
we should then be like...
"Here's 'true blue' and here's"--
And then we'll write another one.
♪ "Baby, I don't feel so good" ♪
♪ Six words you never understood ♪
For some reason it sounds really like
in my head.
Yeah, you're under a towel.
♪ ...say I'm not your type ♪
♪ Just say that I'm not
Your preferred sexual orienta-- ♪
♪ ...-tion
I'm so selfish, oh ♪
♪ But you make me f-- ♪
I think it's sick.
I wanna try one
where you just start this chorus very soft
and in that first phrase, like, hammer it.
Do you know what I mean?
Just, like, get crazy with it,
but start quieter
-or-- or softer or-- or babier.
-'Kay.
Just try it.
♪ How am I supposed to
Make you feel okay ♪
♪ When all you do is walk the other way? ♪
♪ Can you guess ♪
♪ What I'm thinking of ♪
♪ What I'm looking at ♪
♪ Where my eyes came from ♪
♪ Can you guess ♪
♪ What I'm thinking of ♪
♪ What you might become ♪
♪ If you fall in love? ♪
That's a sick hook.
"Can you guess what I'm thinking of. What
you might become if you fall in love?"
That's sick.
-Can you sing it for me?
-It is cool.
But what I'm thinking of is a tattoo.
Yeah, but I think this is
a really good hook.
I mean, it's just like everything else
we've written.
I don't think so.
And also, I just am trying to write
the best song we've ever written
and the most accessible right now,
you know?
That's stupid. You're trying to write
the best song we've ever written?
Absolutely. Every time.
Well, then I'm never gonna do
anything ever if I think that way.
You don't have to think that way,
but I can.
It feels like kind of a minefield to me,
because I feel like I've been,
like, told to write a hit,
but I've been told to not tell Billie
that we have to write a hit.
But Billie hates writing songs in general.
And, you know... is-- I don't know,
so woke about her own...
persona on the Internet
-that I think she's terrified of, like...
-Hate.
...anything that she makes being hated.
And I think her equation is
that the more popular something is,
the more hate it's gonna get.
-Yeah.
-But what I'm trying to do here
specifically is make
the head of A&R at Interscope think,
"Wow, I told them to go write a hit song,
and, in my estimation,
this is kind of a fucking hit."
Mm-hmm.
I don't see how you're gonna do--
get through this without telling her.
You can't trick her into writing a song.
Y'all talking about me?
Just saying that
maybe for the last few songs
that you write for this album...
you could experiment with trying to
make something that you still like
but maybe is a little more conventional
or, you know, accessible, or whatever.
And maybe Finneas
could help guide you with that,
-and it would give you--
-Huh?
For the last few songs that you write
for this album or the next--
What are the words you're using though?
I don't understand.
-Accessible?
-Oh, Pepper!
What does that mean in a song,
writing music-- What does that mean?
-It means, like--
-Accessible means
a song that doesn't alienate anyone
for any reason,
a song that doesn't, like--
But you're literally--
You are both talking about something
that I feel like we've always
talked about as a negative thing
where songs are just, like, for everyone,
anyone can relate.
-I don't-- Honestly-- Okay.
-I don't like that.
You have been telling me that we should
write songs that everyone can relate to.
-I'm not saying that.
-Did he come in here and belittle my idea
-of a song that I was-- that I wrote...
-No.
...that he was trying to turn
into something else
because it's not for everyone?
Is that what happened?
I didn't hear it that way.
I like singing songs.
I like having songs to sing.
And if they have some-- If they mean
something to me, then I like them more.
-But my feeling is that if--
-I hate writing songs,
and I've always hated it.
Every single time I've written a song
that I actually like,
I've hated the process.
I hear that you hate songwriting.
I really-- It really tortures me.
-But what--
-Especially with you
-because you're so good at it.
-But here's what I'd say, if you hate--
I don't wanna blame it on you,
but I hate it.
If you want to stop
writing songs for your next album--
-You don't wanna write any songs?
-I'm not gonna make another album.
♪ Take me to the rooftop ♪
♪ I wanna see the world
When I stop breathing ♪
♪ Turnin' blue ♪
You're gonna go that dark with this song?
Are you seriously implying
that you'd jump off the roof?
Do you feel okay about a song like that?
You don't worry about that?
I feel like it's something
I wanna have said.
-You don't worry about--
-This song is the reason I don't.
Like, having this way of saying it,
instead of doing it, is better.
♪ Taste me, the salty tears on my cheek ♪
♪ That's what a year-long ♪
♪ Headache ♪
Nice.
♪ Does to you ♪
Your head-- If your head was that size
compared to my body in real life...
Yeah. Let's try to interact.
No.
I'm trying to shake your hand.
Hey, Finneas, how are you?
We'll just look right at each other.
-How are you?
-I'm fabulous. Do you like this song?
-I love this song.
-I'm feeling really good about it.
Me too. High five.
Did you finish the album?
I think we finished the album, yeah.
Billie Eilish in studio with us
here on the Kevin and Bean Show.
We have a bunch of questions about
the music we're gonna get to in a minute.
There's one more teenage question
I have to ask.
Are you done with school already
or are you still homeschooling?
-Well--
-Or are you faking homeschooling?
I've never been to school,
so there's a little fact.
-Okay.
-Never--
Never was at school,
so I never had to quit school.
But I graduated, like, last year,
-the beginning of last year.
-What?
But I just, like--
-You're like Doogie Howser. You graduate--
-Who's that?
She doesn't know who Doogie
Howser is. Know your audience.
Who do you feel about
the way your fans feel about you?
See, here's the thing.
Justin Bieber, right?
When I was, like, 12, it wasn't--
I was not a fan of him.
I was a-- I was-- It was--
I was, like--
That was, like, my first love.
Like, that was the person
I was in love with.
-In my head, he was in love with me.
-Of course.
It was like a relationship with a person.
You know when you, like--
you date somebody for a while,
and they're-- that's your partner?
And then you break up with them.
And if you see a picture of them,
without really thinking,
you automatically are like, "Oh, that's
that person I was in a relationship with."
Whoever comes next
is gonna have to deal with the idea
that you were in a relationship
with Justin Bieber.
I wanna play you something right now.
-This is a video of me at 12.
-Okay.
-Nobody's seen this.
-I love this.
I have watched
so many Justin Bieber... things,
I was, like, crying so hard.
'Cause, like, I'm worried
that when I get a boyfriend...
I won't wanna be with him because...
I actually love Justin Bieber more.
And I can't handle that.
I said, "I can't handle that."
I literally remember sobbing into a pillow
because I thought, "I'm never gonna
feel this way about anyone."
I'm-- I literally was terrified
that when I got a boyfriend
when I was older, that I wouldn't--
-He won't compare.
Three sold-out shows
at the Fonda Theatre.
-That's amazing, by the way.
-Thank you.
I know hometown shows
are special for any artist, but I mean...
Hey, Q. Hey.
You look good as hell.
Yo, how are you?
♪ Thought I found a way ♪
♪ Thought I found a way out ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ But you never go away ♪
♪ Never go away ♪
♪ So I guess I gotta stay now ♪
♪ But I hope someday ♪
♪ I'll make it out of here ♪
♪ Even if it takes all night
Or a hundred years ♪
♪ Need a place to hide
But I can't find one near ♪
♪ Wanna feel alive
Outside I can't fight my fear ♪
Love you, Billie. Happy 17th birthday.
Bro, he's so fine. Oh, my God.
♪ Tear me to pieces, skin to bone ♪
Amazing.
Okay, guys. It's a wrap.
♪ Hello, welcome home ♪
Do we have a hose?
For your car?
Yes, but ask your dad about that
because he'll know which hose
he would prefer that you use.
-All right, this is nice. And jet.
-Wait. Go back to that one.
-I'm gonna do the inside.
-Jet is the hardest and cone is--
I mean, center is...
If you go in there,
is it gonna get in there or something?
No, it's built to ride in the rain.
I can't believe
my dream car is in my driveway.
Of course,
these fools come and buy it for me.
I looked at them,
I was like, "You guys are insane.
We have nowhere to park it.
We can't afford to insure it.
It's too fast a car."
And as I talked to them, they were like,
"We're getting the car
with all the safety bells and whistles.
Every safety feature you could have.
It's not the souped-up engine."
She doesn't know that.
It would be like something sh--
You're evil.
♪ Hey, call me back ♪
♪ When you get this ♪
Saying goodbye to the car.
Going on tour. Missing her car.
Love you. Have a good time with Kaylee.
Love you. I'm gonna miss you.
♪ Maybe just forget it ♪
♪ 'Cause by the time you get this ♪
♪ Your number might be blocked ♪
♪ Stay ♪
♪ And blah, blah, blah ♪
♪ You just want what you can't have ♪
♪ No way ♪
♪ I'll call the cops ♪
♪ If you don't stop, I'll call your dad ♪
Ah-one, ah-two,
ah-one, two, three, four!
♪ And I hate to do this to you
On your birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday, by the way ♪
♪ It's not you, it's me
And all that other bullshit ♪
♪ You know that's bullshit ♪
♪ Don't you, babe? ♪
♪ I'm not your party favor ♪
This is so weird, you guys. I'm nobody.
I don't know why you like me.
I really don't.
I really don't know why, but I love you.
And I really hope you guys
feel the way about the album that I feel
because I fucking love it so much.
You're not even ready. Okay.
"Xanny," to both of us,
was a song about, like...
being close to people
that are self-destructive.
Drugs and, you know,
cigarettes are...
-Alcohol...
-...are you killing yourself.
What do you both think about
talking about your feelings about drugs
and cigarettes and alcohol?
My only thought is how, like,
you say things,
and then maybe you...
grow up and feel differently
and then get dragged for it.
-But--
-I have my moment,
and then I do drugs,
and then people are like,
-"Ha-ha. Remember when she said"--
-Wait a second.
Are you actually not gonna let her
be authentic to who she is now
in case she grows up to do drugs?
I don't mean doing any of that--
-Can you do this, please?
-Well--
Stop yelling at Chelsea.
I am not yelling. I just think
that's borrowing trouble. And--
She's right though. She has a point.
Well, maybe don't grow up to do that.
Do you have to plan right now
that you're--
every person who does what you do
has to grow up and fuck up that way?
And you have to plan it so that you
don't get hate later when you do it
because when you were younger,
you said you wouldn't?
You know, why are your parents
with you all the time?
I mean, you've got a whole army of people
trying to help you
not decide to destroy your life
like people in your shoes
have done before.
So, are we gonna literally
not release something
for fear that later she will do that?
I mean, it's what the song is about.
Oh, my God. You're so hot.
♪ Bite my tongue, bide my time ♪
♪ Wearing a warning sign ♪
♪ Wait till the world is mine ♪
♪ Visions I vandalize ♪
♪ Cold in my kingdom size ♪
♪ Fell for these ocean eyes ♪
♪ You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ I'm gonna run this nothing town ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
One by one by one ♪
♪ One by one by one
You should see me in a crown ♪
♪ Your silence is my favorite sound ♪
♪ Watch me make 'em bow
One by one by one ♪
♪ One by one by one ♪
Her new album drops on March 29th.
Every month she logs 21 million hits
on Spotify.
13.2 million followers on Instagram.
Every concert is sold out
two days before going public.
In Zurich, she'll be performing
in Halle 622...
for the 17-year-old Billie Eilish.
So nice to have you here, Billie.
-Hi.
-How are you?
I'm so good.
-I'm so glad that you are here. Yeah.
-So good. I'm glad I'm here too.
Aren't you that tired?
I... I am that tired.
That's a good way of putting it.
Yes, I'm very tired.
-Okay, Billie.
-Yeah?
Next billboard session.
-Where's this gonna be?
-You know, like, how the--
you saw the first round of billboards
-with the album cover?
-Everywhere? Yeah.
-This is the second round of those.
-Okay.
I like--
Hold on. Something's happening here.
Wow! Wow!
What is it?
-An-- A tic attack. No.
-Water?
I don't know why though.
It's been, like, coming on all day,
but I can't, like...
Do you want oil?
Yeah. Mom, do you have the essential oils?
-Essential oils.
-Yes.
Put it on your pulses too, if you can.
Okay.
-Yeah, those are in some--
-Everything looks folded--
Okay.
I don't know why the lights
are, like, really making me, like...
Well, you're also really tired probably.
-Yeah.
-That's probably what it really is.
I've done some crazy shit
'cause of my Tourette's.
I fucking broke a glass once,
in my mouth, because of 'em.
'Cause I have this one
where I'll bite down on something,
like, if I have something,
I'll just go, really hard,
just 'cause my brain is like, "Do it!"
♪ I don't wanna be you... ♪
I'm lonely on Valentine's Day.
-Miserable. So sad.
-Q doesn't do anything?
Haven't gotten... anything.
And the night before, he'd been
really weird and distant and shit. And...
It was totally fine.
We've been great. It's just, like--
But then they had this plan
to go to Big Bear, like all--
like, the whole squad
was gonna go to Big Bear.
I was like, "You know what?
Have fun. Don't worry about me.
I'm miserable and I miss you,
and I wish you would talk to me,
and I have no one else to talk to,
but I'm chillin'.
So, have fun. Shoo."
♪ ...that told you so ♪
♪ Sorry, sorry ♪
♪ I'm sorry, sorry ♪
♪ Psych, bitch! ♪
♪ By the way ♪
♪ You've been uninvited ♪
♪ 'Cause all you say... ♪
Stop!
♪ Are all the same things... ♪
Let's go!
♪ Copycat tryna cop my manner ♪
♪ Watch your back
When you can't watch mine ♪
I can't do shows anymore.
My legs hurt too bad.
-I can't do it. I just can't jump.
-Okay.
-It's so, so painful.
-Why don't you sit down right now
and have a little massage?
Oh, my God.
Like, walking right now is so painful.
There. How to do it.
I'm afraid I'll wake up
and I won't have any of this anymore.
Everything I've ever loved,
I've had to quit.
I used to dance,
like, 12 hours a week.
And then I got injured.
I tore my growth plate in my hip.
The bone separated from the muscle.
It was the most depressing year
of my life.
I just laid in bed. I couldn't move.
Since then I have not danced.
-Do you want a hand, Patrick?
-Yeah, one second.
My little announcement before we move on.
I have shin splints...
and I threw my neck out.
So-- Listen though, listen.
It hurts really bad to jump,
but I'm a dumbass, so I'm gonna jump.
♪ My boy, my boy, my boy ♪
♪ He ain't a man and sure as hell-- ♪
♪ Don't love me like he promised ♪
♪ My boy, my boy, my boy ♪
-Ow!
-Doctor's orders.
Every two to three hours,
five to ten minutes of stretching,
15 minutes of icing.
You can do it, Billie.
How do people not miss me?
I just wanna know.
They don't miss me?
I would miss me.
"We're gonna miss you so much."
-Sure.
-I bet they miss you, Billie.
Nope.
You know, it's painful to miss people.
And so our brains
come up with coping strategies for it.
Why can't we just miss people though?
Why do we have to cope?
Why can't we just let it happen?
-Because it hurts. It's painful.
-So?
Let it hurt.
I want people to hurt
because they miss me.
I don't want them to just act
like they don't miss me at all, and...
It's already 3:30, and I know
you have a lot of people to meet.
-Mom, we're not even there yet.
-I know, I'm just reminding you
that you don't have a lot of time
to not talk.
Can I just not do anything
and just walk around this park alone?
That would be fun.
People are always, like, you know,
"It's so dark. Like, have happy music."
I'm like, "But I'm never feeling happy.
So why would I write about things
I don't know about?"
You know, I feel the dark things.
I feel them very strongly.
And, you know, why would I...
not talk about them,
you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, and your fans seem to notice that.
A couple of days ago, we interviewed
a teenage band from around here,
and they said they liked your music,
and they said, "If you listen carefully,
you can even listen to her
on the brink of crying even."
So you transmit it to the people.
Do you think that that's the reason why
your music is resonating so much
with your own generation?
To have a song
that is describing exactly how you feel
is just the best feeling in the world.
'Cause it makes you feel comforted.
It makes you feel like there's--
like you're not alone, you know?
In your music, I sense
a kind of idea of a fantasy,
of a built-up world of your own.
You can perceive it,
but you cannot describe it.
Do you have any image in your mind
of this kind of new world
you want to create
with your lyrics, your sounds?
There are things
that you can feel and not describe.
And it's not like,
"Oh, I don't have words for this."
It's more like, you--
there's literally no words
to describe that feeling.
It's like how we all
are drawn to dangerous situations
because they're intriguing and
we don't know what's on the other side,
and, like, music is that.
You love it because you love it,
and that's it.
You don't really have a reason
why you love it, you just do.
♪ You can pretend you don't miss me ♪
♪ You can pretend you don't care ♪
♪ All you wanna do is kiss me ♪
♪ Oh, what a shame, I'm not there ♪
♪ You can pretend you don't miss me ♪
♪ You can pretend you don't care ♪
♪ All you wanna do is kiss me ♪
♪ Oh, what a shame... ♪
I love you!
♪ Everybody knows ♪
♪ You and I are suicide and stolen art ♪
♪ Art ♪
♪ Pretty mama sews ♪
♪ Stitches into
All your bitches' broken hearts ♪
♪ You can pretend you don't miss me ♪
♪ You can pretend you don't care ♪
This is the last show
on this tour, bro. What the hell?
Oh, my God.
It's the end of an era, man.
But my album comes out soon though.
♪ Somebody new is gonna comfort you ♪
♪ Like you want me to
Every now and then, it hits me ♪
♪ That I'm the one that got away ♪
♪ But I guess bein' lonely... ♪
Damn, I wanted to see you today. Fuck.
I wanted to see you today too. What?
You're so fine.
I love you. I'm in love with you.
I love you.
-I love you!
-I love you.
You have
a lot of interesting things going on,
in terms of being hypermobile,
having these tics
and having a really challenging
physical lifestyle.
Mm-hmm.
It's sort of a sandwich of things
that is just gonna make it
even more important for you
to be really good with self-care.
If you don't carve out the space
in your life to take care of yourself,
no one else is gonna do it.
They're all just gonna be like,
"But, Billie, do this, do that."
It's already like that.
Justin's fanboying over you right now.
Justin Bieber?
He's kinda obsessed with you right now,
really wants to work with you.
I think if you wanted to do
a "bad guy" song with him,
a remix, we could do that.
But honestly, it doesn't even matter to me
'cause you don't need it.
I just thought it was funny.
Yeah, but how does Billie
-reply to his DM?
-How do I reply if he says,
"I wanna be on your album"?
-Because--
-Just say, "Ha-ha,
my album comes out in three days,
but if you wanna jump on 'bad guy'"--
Or I dunno.
What do you feel comfortable saying?
I do not feel comfortable doing--
saying no in any sort of way
at all to him.
There's no way.
He could ask me to kill my dog
and I would. I don't even think--
Well, between you and I, what do you want?
Do you wanna do anything with him?
Yeah! The fuck? Obviously.
Do you wanna do
a new song with him and, like...
No, I do not wanna work with him.
I do not wanna work with him.
-No, no, no, no.
-Would--
-Do you want him to jump on "bad guy"?
-Yes, but a remix though.
I said, "You could literally
hop on the song and just say 'poop'
and I'd be happy with it."
Billie Eilish
is out with a new album today--
17-year-old sensation. Her debut album...
...most talked about teenager in music...
Not only one of
the most important releases for March
but maybe of the year.
Her album is called When We
All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?
Billie Eilish.
We put up Australia and New Zealand,
and it sold out in five minutes.
The album is number one
in 37 countries right now.
♪ White shirt now red, my bloody nose ♪
♪ Sleepin', you're on your tippy-toes ♪
♪ Creepin' around like no one knows ♪
♪ Think you're so criminal ♪
Yeah!
You know, it's so amazing to watch you.
To have watched you get to this point.
Billie. NME just reviewed your album.
Five out of five stars.
Really? Fire.
Hello!
♪ I like it when you take control ♪
What's up, girl? You look fresh tonight.
You're breaking Spotify records.
You're breaking Apple Music records.
Are you ready for
the next level of superstardom?
-No.
-No?
My album comes out
in, like, two seconds, basically.
And...
A whole-- It's out. Yeah!
♪ If she reads all the lyrics
She'll pity the men I know ♪
♪ So you're a tough guy
Like it really rough guy ♪
♪ Just can't get enough guy
Chest always so puffed guy ♪
♪ I'm that bad type
Make your mama sad type ♪
♪ Make your girlfriend mad tight
Might seduce your dad type ♪
♪ I'm the bad guy ♪
It's a number one album.
And I have a red Tesla
in front of the house.
Oh, my gosh.
-I love you.
Thanks for making the album with me.
You know that she said today she--
A year ago,
she had a million followers on Instagram.
That's crazy.
-That's a lot in a year.
-It is.
-Anyway, it was more--
-Where we at now?
Fif-- almost 16 million.
-♪ I'm better off without them ♪
-♪ Without them ♪
♪ They're nothing but unstable ♪
Here's your Spotify.
-Is that million?
-Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I thought that was thousand.
I was like, lemme see--
No.
720 million.
That's nuts, dude.
Who you texting, Q?
Uh-huh.
Hi, baby.
There's like 40 brands
that have sent me a Coachella outfit.
It's honestly crazy.
Where are you right now?
Hungover?
You didn't drive home, right?
You did?
Why?
You said you wouldn't do that.
I'm mad that you did that shit.
At least I told you.
I know. I'm glad you told me,
but I don't want you to do that.
You don't take me seriously
when I say that.
I just want you safe.
You know that.
I'm seeing you tonight, okay?
Okay. I love you.
Bye, baby.
Bye.
We maybe have a couple
more press looks, and then we're done.
I had a dream that Coachella was horrible
and the worst thing ever
and it ruined my career.
♪ Lips meet teeth and tongue ♪
♪ My heart skips eight beats at once ♪
During the beginning of "bad guy,"
I'll go to the front of the stage
and be like, "What's up?"
I'll probably thank the dancers here.
-Yeah.
-Once the mic is in,
I want it to be pretty quick.
These bitches can go super fast.
♪ ...watch your car burn ♪
♪ With the fire that you started in me ♪
♪ But you never came back to ask it out ♪
♪ Go ahead and watch my heart burn ♪
The wall screens?
I don't want it to be, you know,
a blue song and then there's pink.
First of all, I hate pink.
Never use pink ever.
I think that you don't understand
how special it is
to focus on you on that song.
You might wanna consider
having a different visual than the video.
My favorite thing during
a festival show is looking at the crowd
and they're not looking at me.
I love that.
It makes me feel way less uncomfortable,
especially at Coachella.
It's not as interesting
as watching Billie sing the song.
I'm gonna be, like,
thousands of feet from people.
People are gonna be so far away.
Especially at this time slot,
and especially with what's going on
in your career right now.
♪ If I could get to sleep
I would have slept by now ♪
I don't wanna go.
That shit is too much pressure.
I don't like pressure.
I don't feel pressure most of the time.
Right now, thousands of people
are pouring into the desert
for the start of Coachella.
It is one of the world's most popular
outdoor music festivals.
Coachella is the world's
highest-grossing music festival.
125,000 concertgoers a day.
Is Q coming?
I said, "I'm getting you tickets for this,
and the deal is
that you have to spend time with me.
You have to see me
if I'm gonna let you come for free."
"Of course." Haven't seen him
in two and a half days.
We're at this Interscope party.
The one I was saying I was taking you to,
but then you didn't come.
I wanted you to be here, damn it.
My ass was alone the whole day. It's okay.
Hey, Q.
Look at the hair.
Go ahead.
Q, okay, ready? Help me.
So it's either...
I'm putting my teeth in.
You know I don't have to wear mine
anymore during the day.
Really?
That's why you look so goddamn good.
You should've did your hair
with the things again.
-Should I? I was thinking about it.
-Yeah.
-Could you still do it?
-You should. It looked bomb.
-I haven't done the show yet.
-I really think you should.
-You think?
♪ Waking up at sundown ♪
♪ They're late to every party ♪
-She needs to be changing her clothes.
-♪ Nobody's ever sorry ♪
I'm doing it.
♪ Too inebriated now to dance ♪
♪ Morning as they come down ♪
♪ Their pretty heads are hurting ♪
-♪ They're awfully bad at learning ♪
-Is this rehearsing the lyrics?
-Yeah.
-♪ Make the same mistakes ♪
♪ Blame... ...circumstance ♪
♪ I'm ♪
♪ In their secondhand smoke ♪
-Change now.
-Okay.
Bro, I wish I could sing like that.
Like...
Why she sing so fire?
♪ Circumstance ♪
-I love you.
-Love you too.
-Go.
-All right, eat your pizza.
I gotta warm up.
Danny wants to bring Katy Perry
to say hi to you.
I'm so good. How are you?
I gotta confess about my fiancé.
-I am--
-I'm a huge fan obviously.
But my fiancé,
-who doesn't listen to--
-Hello.
-He listens to a lot of music.
-I literally had you--
He literally will only play you
in the car.
"Bad guy."
All the time.
-♪ I'm such a bad guy ♪
-Thank you, bro.
-♪ Treat you like a rough guy ♪
-Yee!
There it goes.
-I wanna take a picture.
-How are you?
-I'm doing good.
-So proud of you.
-Congrats.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-And I love you, and...
I wanted to say that
this is gonna be wild for ten years.
It's gonna be crazy.
If you ever wanna talk,
'cause it's a weird ride.
I know.
-It's a-- Yes.
-I know you know.
-Good for you.
-Yeah.
-You're amazing.
-Amazing.
-Who was that?
-Orlando Bloom?
-So-- Oh, really?
-He played--
He played Will Turner
in fucking Pirates of the Caribbean.
-That guy?
-That was him.
-That was him?
-Yeah, that's him.
There's all these TMZ photos
of her and him paddleboarding together.
Wait, those are full-on nudes.
Let me see.
-Let me see.
-Who is that?
-Orlando Bloom.
-That was him?
-He's outside still.
-Why is it so skinny?
No way!
I wouldn't know anything about that.
Bring him back. I wanna meet him again.
He kissed me on the cheek.
That's Orlando Bloom.
I did not know that was him. I thought
that was just some dude Katy Perry met.
Oh, my God!
I love you, baby.
-I love you, Mama.
-Have a good time.
-Enjoy it.
-Yeah, have a great time.
-Just enjoy yourself.
-Ready, Brian?
That's all that matters, okay?
-You're very brave and amazing.
-I love you.
-I love you so much.
-You are very brave.
I'm not brave.
Billie! Billie!
Billie! Billie! Billie! Billie!
Dad.
There isn't room for another human
out there. It's unbelievable.
-Is it going okay out there?
-Oh, yeah. Well, yeah.
Billie, Billie, Billie! Oh, I'm so happy--
Wait. Will you wait?
I've gotta use the toilet.
I don't wanna miss it.
Dude.
-You are so--
-This is the universe hugging you.
I'm giving you
so much love and light right now.
You don't even understand.
My nine-year-old self, bro--
You're a fucking...
Oh, no. Oh, my lord!
-Thank you for everything you do.
-Oh, I love you.
I love you.
-Okay.
-I've been literally climbing mountains
listening to your music. I love it.
Now I know.
Billie! Billie! Billie!
What is going on?
Fuck the screen!
Fuck the screen! Fuck the screen!
We're probably gonna
have to cut "xanny." But that's it.
-What?
-Probably have to cut "xanny" for time.
So we're losing "xanny" and something.
"WHEN I WAS OLDER" probably, right?
Let's go. Here we go. Bill, Andrew.
If anything's going wrong,
act like it's not.
Billie! Billie! Billie!
...nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two, one.
Roll show.
Look at the screen.
Bro, what is happening?
Just remember they're here to see you.
-What?
-Just remember they're here to see you.
They're not even gonna see me
if the screen doesn't work.
-They're gonna have the lights on.
-For fuck's sake.
Coachella!
Holy fuck!
♪ Look at you needing me ♪
♪ You know I'm just... ♪
Fuck!
♪ Begging for our help ♪
What the fuck are the words though?
-♪ Poisoning themselves now ♪
-Bro.
♪ Begging for our help ♪
♪ Wow! ♪
♪ Hills burn in California ♪
♪ My turn to ignore ya ♪
♪ Don't say I didn't warn ya ♪
♪ All the good girls go to hell ♪
♪ I wanna end me ♪
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
♪ What do you want from me? ♪
♪ Why don't you run from me? ♪
♪ What are you wondering? ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ Why aren't you scared of me? ♪
♪ Why do you care for me? ♪
♪ When we all fall asleep
Where do we go? ♪
Billie! Billie! Billie!
All right, so for this song...
I just want...
us all to be in the moment for this song,
because I feel like, in life,
we tend to do things and then...
We're always looking forward to the
next thing and the next thing after that.
We're never thinking about
what's happening right now.
And this is happening right now,
and this is crazy.
And, like...
we-- and I...
are never gonna be in this moment
ever again, no matter what.
This exact moment right here.
Never again. Ever.
This is the only chance
we get to be in the moment.
So why don't we be in the moment, yeah?
All right, let's do it.
♪ Don't you know I'm no good for you? ♪
♪ I've learned to lose
You can't afford to ♪
♪ Tore my shirt to stop you bleeding ♪
♪ But nothing ever stops you leaving ♪
♪ Quiet when I'm comin' home
And I'm on my own ♪
♪ I could lie, say I like it like that
Like it like that ♪
♪ Don't you know too much already? ♪
♪ I'll only hurt you if you let me ♪
♪ Call me friend but keep me closer ♪
Call me back.
♪ And I'll call you
When the party's over ♪
♪ Quiet when I'm comin' home
And I'm on my own ♪
♪ And I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ And I could lie
Say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
♪ But nothin' is better sometimes ♪
♪ Once we've both said our goodbyes ♪
♪ Let's just let it go ♪
♪ Let me let you go ♪
♪ Quiet when I'm comin' home
And I'm on my own ♪
♪ I could lie, say I like it like that ♪
♪ Like it like that ♪
Thank you.
You know, the screen came back eventually.
"Bury a friend" was fucking crazy.
I know. Billie killed it.
They loved the new stuff.
At the end of the day,
kids were standing there
to see Billie Eilish,
and you're Billie Eilish.
-Yeah.
-And you killed it, you know what I mean?
You did exactly what, like,
everyone wanted.
You guys, that was amazing.
-Oh, thank you.
-It was. Your performance was spectacular.
You killed it.
You didn't seem nervous at all.
-No, it was a beautiful--
-I just wasn't happy with it.
-What?
-I was not happy with the way I was.
You were amazing.
I was so excited for
"all the good girls go to hell,"
and then I bombed the shit out of it.
It was fine and funny.
-I love you. Amazing.
-You really did great.
-Billie, you're amazing.
-That was fantastic!
It was amazing.
I wish you could feel what we felt.
People were thrilled.
People were just like, "A star.
She's a superstar. It's amazing."
People loved it so much.
And that's what you can do
with everything going down around you.
You forgot some words
to a new song. Big deal.
Who cares?
Hello.
Where are you?
Can you come here?
Can't you see me?
What do you mean, "try"?
Hello?
I'm just blaming you
for the beeping 'cause I like it.
Good morning, my sweetheart.
You were amazing last night.
I love you.
♪ Ain't no holding back guy ♪
♪ Come off like I'm mad guy
Always got your back guy ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm the real type
Keep you full of thrills type ♪
♪ Show you what it feels like
Got an open invite ♪
♪ I'm the bad guy, woah-ooh ♪
Billie, that's gotta be
pretty amazing for you.
-That's crazy that's his voice.
-Justin Bieber's voice.
♪ Gold teeth, my neck ♪
♪ My wrist is froze
I got more ice than... ♪
You're gonna cry?
Because she's cried
over Justin Bieber's songs
so much over the years,
-and he's singing their song now.
-Yeah.
He's singing your song.
I hear he's here this weekend.
He is.
Coachella!
Let me hear you all.
Oh, there you are.
Oh! Justin Bieber!
Justin! Justin!
I just saw his eyebrow,
and I know his face.
I know everything about him.
He was born at St. Jude's Hospital
on March 1st, at 12:56 a.m.,
on the second floor.
-Holy fuck.
-Enough.
-Yeah, where were you born?
-I have no idea.
He came over to me
and I ran away from him.
And he just stood there
and looked at me...
I know. You ran away.
-...with his eyes.
-You pivoted away.
He looked at you with his eyes?
-His eyes.
That's so amazing, Billie.
And I literally cried in his arms
for, like, five minutes,
like...
And every time I would do this,
kind of, like,
like, you could feel it,
and he would just squeeze me.
You know what that's like.
It happens to you every meet and greet.
Yeah, you know exactly how you--
How... you know,
it feels to be him in that situation.
"It's moments like tonight,
where I'm reminded what I mean to people.
Your love for me touched my heart.
You are so special.
Not for what you can do,
but for who you are.
-Remember that."
-Damn.
"I'm so impressed
by your aura and presence.
You carry a heavy calling.
You are an idol to so many.
I'm excited to watch you flourish.
You are beyond special.
Thank you for tonight.
It meant just as much to me
as it meant to you.
I also want to let you know
that it feels like yesterday"--
"It feels like yesterday I was singing"--
Oh, "Yesterday I was 15,
singing 'One Time,'
and now I'm 25, and that was ten years ago
and it flew by like a flash.
Enjoy every minute
of what you are experiencing."
"Embrace it all, believe, you are great,
but not greater than anyone."
Bill, you gotta be friends with him.
You have to.
-Yeah.
-Gosh.
Seriously.
Let's talk about--
Let's talk about people that value you.
People that give you value.
♪ 'Cause everything starts
From something ♪
♪ But something would be nothing ♪
♪ Nothing if your heart didn't dream
With me ♪
♪ 'Cause everything starts
From something ♪
♪ But something would be nothing ♪
♪ Nothing if your heart didn't dream
With me ♪
♪ Where would I be ♪
♪ If you didn't believe? ♪
♪ I know you got your wall ♪
♪ Wrapped all the way around your heart ♪
♪ Don't have to be scared at all
Oh, my love ♪
♪ But you can't fly unless you let your ♪
♪ You can't fly
Unless you let yourself fall ♪
♪ I will catch you if you fall ♪
♪ But if you spread your wings
You can fly away with me ♪
♪ You can't fly unless you let yourself ♪
♪ Let yourself fall ♪
As a little kid,
I considered taking her to therapy.
I mean, there were days, driving--
I remember driving her to dance class
and just thinking,
"How are we gonna cope with this?
How are we gonna cope?"
She's lovesick, you know.
Just like desperately in love
with Justin Bieber.
So, to meet him...
And we all--
The whole family went to see Believe.
I think we went
on Christmas Day to see it,
or Never Say Never, one of them.
Whole family went,
then we-- whole family saw the next one.
I mean, and we all thought he was amazing,
like, we never were--
We were never in the... the "hater" camp,
of which sadly for every person
in the world, there is...
anyone who's talented or amazing.
But we were never that, we're always like,
"Wow, this kid's amazing,
he's so talented.
He works so hard."
So, you know...
She couldn't process it.
You could just see her standing there.
She couldn't-- She couldn't take it in.
I mean, she sobbed in his arms, you know?
She was crying,
and he was so sweet to her,
and it meant so much to her.
And it seems to have meant a lot to him,
which is--
I don't know, I felt so--
You know, you feel--
Your heart kinda breaks for him,
because he's 25 years old,
that is so young
you can't even process how young that is.
And he's just been through so much,
and he's screwed up
a lot and he came back, and--
screwed up and he's found
this girl that he loves and--
He's really sad, you know.
I honestly don't know how
any artist of any age
with this kind of trajectory
is doing it without a parent, you know?
Like, someone who loves you
more than life itself
and would do anything for you, like how--
And there's nobody-- You can't pay
someone to do that, you know?
I mean-- And--
And we come as close as we can.
I think that the people on her team
do love her that way,
and they would do anything for her, but--
You know. Like I say, they can't--
They can't see her
in the middle of the night.
They can't see her in the morning.
Can't see how
she's coping or feeling.
When you think of
your mental health journey,
what comes to mind?
Being really bad
at taking care of my mental health.
I'm a person who wants
to make things better
for other people and make--
You know, do the right thing
no matter what it's doing to me.
And--
Or whether it is the right thing at all.
The right thing should be
what's right for you.
Q is at the emergency room.
Why?
'Cause he broke his hand,
'cause he punched a wall.
Jesus Christ.
And I'm trying to get him
to go to therapy.
He's so self-destructive.
That's really scary. I'm sorry.
All right, so we're fitting for tour,
and then we have this
ASCAP thing on Thursday,
which is like a red carpet.
And then I think that's kinda it.
It's just a lot of looks for tour.
Hard.
How do you wipe yourself with these?
Just like you.
When she gets...
I'm worried.
'Cause he's talking to her a long time,
like he's explaining something
to do better.
Did you pass?
Yes.
How was it?
It was fine. It was so easy.
Can you have passengers now?
-No, only when I'm 18.
-Eighteen?
But I can be alone though.
That's what's important.
Yeah, because there's so many places
you can go alone.
I can go to my people's houses.
Which, by the way, I'm going to. Today.
Doing what?
I wanna go see Q and his broken hand.
I heard he broke his hand 'cause
he was angry and he punched the wall.
Yeah.
You don't want him getting angry at you.
No, he never does it to anyone.
It's only a... other thing.
So you know that
when you're alone in the car
and nobody's there to say anything to you,
the rules of law still apply.
It's not now you get to speed
and do all kind of stupid shit.
Yeah.
So, you've been, you know--
You've learned to drive,
and you've been coached
and helped and tested...
in order to be sure that you're
going to be a sober, sensible driver.
So, slow down. Try to figure it out.
If you make a wrong turn, go around,
come back, and make the right turn.
Don't swerve across the freeway
and suddenly stop in the median, right?
All the things
we've been talking about all this time.
Yeah.
But now
that you're navigating on your own...
you'll have a heightened sense of,
I believe, anxiety,
so always just
err on the side of being safe.
"Whoops...
I went down the wrong entrance ramp,
so I gotta go down another mile
and turn around."
Okay.
-I love you.
-Love you.
I go.
So long.
All these things aren't sudden,
for the most part, you know?
Her childhood went somewhere a while ago.
Well, there's not much to it,
but it is-- It's profound.
And I think for her, you know,
it's, you know, the future.
Everybody feels that way
when you get a license.
You're off to see
what your life turns into.
So... yeah.
You know, and then we just
live in denial, as always.
'Cause you can't
think about it too hard...
or you won't let her
do anything, you know?
I mean, I was-- I had a drink of something
and I completely choked on it, like water.
I had some yesterday.
It came out my nose and my eyes teared up,
and I was like, it's remarkable
that we stay alive, at all.
Yeah, we're this delicate system.
And, you know, it's remarkable that we...
You have to have faith,
you have to do your best,
and live your best life and...
and then you have to live in denial.
'Cause what else?
Alternative is you can't do anything.
Can't have a boyfriend,
you can't have a car,
you can't go anywhere.
It's unacceptable.
We all did it.
Anyway.
-Where's Billie?
-She done gone.
-She did?
-Yeah.
Just to drive around?
No, she's gone gone.
Oh. I thought she was gonna
come talk to me first.
You were on the phone.
I told her
she could come say something though.
I said she can come talk to me.
Well, that makes me sad.
Well, I'm sorry.
You were in an important phone call.
No, but I literally said
she can come talk to me.
Okay. Well, I can't call her.
She's driving a car.
Did she go to the... guy's house?
-She's going to the studio.
-Which is where?
West Hollywood, like, near--
She's going to West Hollywood?
Yes.
She said he lived in North Hollywood.
We've never known where he lives.
I wanted her to put the thing on
where you can follow someone's phone,
you know?
You can find where they are,
just for safety purposes, you know?
'Cause I don't think she has that
on her phone and Finneas did,
so you could always be like,
"Oh, this is where she is," you know?
Find Your Friends app?
Yeah, probably.
All right. I thought she did.
On my last tour, when I had
shin splints and a sprained ankle
and I threw out my neck
and everything, like...
there was a moment
where I was in so much pain,
that it was the first time I've ever
thought that I had to cancel a show.
Not because, "Oh, I'm in too much pain,"
it was more, like,
"I can't do the show I want to.
I can't give you
the show that I wanna give you."
And it's like, my favorite part
about all this is the shows.
You say these shows are, like, everything,
but you posted before the Europe trip,
like, "I don't wanna go,"
or "Take me home,"
-whatever, on Instagram.
-True.
So, is it... What is it?
Do you love it, do you hate it?
Is it a combination of both?
It is really difficult to leave
the people that you love.
Leaving the people that need me
is so hard to do.
Hi, Billie!
-Hello...
-Oh, my God. I love you.
-Billie, can I have a photo?
-Yes. Go for it.
-I'm gonna cry.
-Billie.
Wait, are you getting a photo with her?
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much. I love you so much.
Oh, shit!
I love you! I love you!
♪ You better hurry ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm leavin' soon ♪
♪ Sorry can't save me now ♪
♪ Sorry I don't know how ♪
♪ Sorry there's no way out ♪
♪ But down ♪
♪ Mmm, down ♪
♪ Call my friends
And tell them that I love them ♪
♪ And I'll miss them ♪
♪ But I'm not sorry ♪
♪ Call my friends
And tell them that I love them ♪
♪ And I'll miss them ♪
♪ Sorry ♪
I've always been that kind of person
that needs to be around friends.
That's probably been
the hardest thing in touring.
It's just not being able
to be around friends, so, like,
with this tour,
I was able to bring a friend out.
It doesn't make me happy
to be lonely all the time,
so I'm working on it.
Billie Eilish.
We promised you we'd get her on.
-Good morning, Billie.
-Hey, Billie.
Good morning. How ya doin'?
We went to Coachella,
me and the girlfriend.
The girlfriend
freaked at your performance.
Everyone loves you.
You're 17 years old,
and you're owning the world.
That must be mental, right?
It's crazy, dude.
-UNO.
-No UNO!
This has been, like,
the first tour that's actually been fun.
And I don't mean the shows,
'cause the shows are always fun,
but I just feel, like, this tour...
It's just been good.
♪ Sitting all alone ♪
♪ Mouth full of gum ♪
♪ In the driveway ♪
♪ My friends aren't far ♪
♪ In the back of my car ♪
♪ Lay their bodies ♪
♪ Where's my mind? ♪
♪ They'll be here pretty soon ♪
♪ Looking through my room ♪
♪ For the money ♪
♪ I'm biting my nails ♪
♪ I'm too young to go to jail ♪
♪ It's kinda funny ♪
♪ Where's my mind? ♪
Let's go!
♪ Maybe it's in the gutter ♪
♪ Where I left my lover ♪
♪ What an expensive fake ♪
♪ My V is for Vendetta ♪
♪ Thought that I'd feel better ♪
♪ But now I got a bellyache ♪
-Hello?
-Where are you?
I'm driving right now.
-Yes. Yeah!
-I miss you.
-Hello?
I miss you. I miss you.
I will see...
Let me call you
when I'm done driving, baby.
-I love you, baby.
-All right, babe.
Call me later, please.
Please?
Sev.
Fuck.
It's a hard time for teenagers, I think.
I think people give teenagers
a really rough time,
'cause they're like...
"Oh, they're privileged,
and why are they--
They have it so easy,"
and, "Why are-- They're fake-depressed."
And it's, like, no, there's a lot
to be depressed about right now.
If you're a teenager,
you're dealing with parents
probably who lived
through the recession, like us,
who've been scared
that they're gonna lose their homes,
or, you know, have financial hardship.
You lose-- Living in a culture with
an opioid epidemic and a drug epidemic.
You're facing, possibly,
the destruction of the planet.
You're in a political climate
that is terrifying...
racist climate, hateful...
You know, it is
a horrible time to be a teenager,
and people are like, "Oh, you know,
Billie Eilish's music is depressing."
It's, like, no, kids are depressed.
It's a scary time.
♪ When I'm away from you ♪
♪ I'm happier than ever ♪
♪ Don't you think it's ever... ♪
Hard. Ooh.
How about the whole song
is just more, like...
nothing even specific that they did.
You're just not happy being with them.
-I love that.
-You can't even explain it.
Like, say, like,
"I can't-- I can't explain it."
♪ When I'm away from you ♪
-♪ I'm happier than ever ♪
-♪ Than ever ♪
♪ Wish I could explain it better ♪
♪ Wish it wasn't true ♪
Okay, okay, I think I'm good.
Are you recording it?
♪ When I'm away from you ♪
♪ I'm happier than ever ♪
I just wasn't happy.
And I didn't want
the same things he wanted,
and I don't think that's fair for him.
I don't think
you should be in a relationship,
super excited about certain things
the other person couldn't care less about.
I don't think that's fair to you.
So I don't think that was--
I didn't think that was fair to him.
And there was just a lack of...
effort, I think?
I literally was just like,
"Dude, you don't even
have enough love to love yourself.
You can't love me, dude."
Like... And you don't.
Like, you think you do.
I do love him, though,
which is what made it harder.
'Cause I'm not over him.
I didn't find someone else.
I didn't, like, stop having love for him.
I just, like, spent time
away from him for a little bit,
and I was like,
"Wow, I'm missing so much, because I'm,
like, I-- I'm worried about you
all the time,
and I don't want what you want,
and, like, you don't want
what I want." And...
I'm not-- I don't need to--
I don't wanna... fix him.
I can't fix him. I've tried.
I can't do it anymore,
like, I don't wanna do it.
I'm just not happy.
♪ He's gone, he's gone ♪
♪ He's gone ♪
♪ You're better off
I'm glad that he's gone ♪
♪ You and me under each other's wing ♪
-That part.
-♪ But he spoiled everything ♪
♪ Bitch, I love you
He never loved you ♪
♪ He never loved you, my baby ♪
♪ Never no tears for that sucker ♪
New York, how ya doin' tonight?
Do y'all feel good?
Good, because...
♪ "Baby, I don't feel so good" ♪
♪ Six words you never understood ♪
♪ "I'll never let you go"
Five words you'll never say ♪
Aw.
♪ I laugh along like nothing's wrong
Four days has never felt so long ♪
♪ If three's a crowd and two was us
One slipped away ♪
♪ I just wanna make you feel okay ♪
♪ But all you do is look the other way ♪
♪ I can't tell you how much
I wish I didn't wanna stay ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I just kinda wish you were gay ♪
♪ Is there a reason we're not through? ♪
♪ Is there a 12-step just for you? ♪
♪ Our conversation's all in blue
11 "heys" ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
♪ Ten fingers tearin' out my hair ♪
♪ Nine times you never made it there ♪
♪ I ate alone at 7:00
You were six minutes away ♪
♪ How am I supposed to
Make you feel okay ♪
♪ When all you do is walk the other way? ♪
♪ I can't tell you how much
I wish I didn't wanna stay ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I just kinda wish you were gay ♪
♪ Maybe won't you take it back ♪
♪ Say you were trying to make me laugh ♪
♪ And nothing has to change today ♪
♪ You didn't mean to say I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ And I don't want to ♪
♪ Up all night ♪
♪ On another red-eye ♪
♪ I wish we never learned to fly ♪
♪ Maybe we should just try ♪
♪ To tell ourselves a good lie ♪
♪ I didn't mean to make you cry ♪
♪ Maybe won't you take it back ♪
♪ Say you were trying to make me laugh ♪
♪ And nothing has to change today ♪
♪ You didn't mean to say I love you ♪
♪ I love you ♪
♪ And I don't want to ♪
♪ The smile that you gave me ♪
♪ Even when you felt like dyin' ♪
♪ We fall apart as it gets dark ♪
♪ I'm in your arms in Central Park ♪
♪ I can't escape the way I love you ♪
♪ And I don't want to ♪
♪ But I love you ♪
-Thank you so much for performing.
-You were beautiful up there.
Really amazing. Really fantastic.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Marty.
-Hey, I'm-- I'm Marty, by the way.
-Nice to meet you.
Hey, Billie. Such a good show.
First group,
are we taking photos with your kids too?
Do you wanna, just, three or four
at a time, or what do you want to do?
Well, whoever's in your group,
bring 'em in.
-Okay.
-Like a group picture.
Okay, that's enough.
I don't know who these people are--
Hey, Saul, where did she go?
Jessica and Ja--
-Billie, just get it over with.
-No!
Just do the "hey, hey, hi"--
They said one group. And then he brought--
He said, "You next.
Next group. Next group."
Every time you leave
it's taking way too much time.
-No, dude. I don't want to do it.
-Come on. Billie. Let's just--
Why do I have to meet
all these fucking randos?
Billie, they're already--
-They're not random.
-Who even are they?
Billie, I don't know.
They're connected with the label somehow.
But every time I go out there, then,
like, three people come up to me.
-Just stay there. Just stay there.
-And there's like a billion of them.
-These random... bitches.
-Billie, they're not random.
They're people connected to people who--
who play your music or whatever.
We don't know why
but just get it over with.
No single shots.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
Camera's right there, Billie.
Group picture, guys.
Hey.
Girl, you look so pretty. I'm a major fan.
Tell Billie. Introduce Billie.
I do promotion. We met briefly.
-Nice to see you again. How are you?
-Okay, fire.
We've seen-- We've met
with him twice in the last two days.
We-- He's at Sirius. He's the one
that plays you on all the channels.
This is the guys from Verizon.
Glen, pleasure to meet you. Great show.
Hello.
-Do you guys want a picture?
-Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
Are you guys working tomorrow?
-Honestly, yeah. I'm here.
-Okay.
Okay, I got a flash on
to make it a little better.
I literally can't have a bad moment.
Where did you see that comment?
It's, like, one person commented
on that picture I posted.
Not even, like, a fan account or anything,
just a random person.
"You were rude at the-- Apparently
you were rude at the meet and greet.
My friend was there and they said you were
rude. You were bothered and you"--
I was like, "Yo." I can't have one moment.
-After my show.
-I mean, it would be great
if you could overcome that
in the moment and just--
-Hey, Mom!
-Listen, I'm just saying.
-I'm giving you complete--
-You know how much I've done that?
I'm giving you complete empathy.
You-- It shouldn't happen--
I can't have one moment where I'm like,
"You know what? I don't wanna do this."
Not one. I've never had one moment,
and I had one moment.
And there it is written about.
It's, like, that--
You were failed by me
and your whole team yesterday.
I'd love to meet your kids.
But I don't want to be shoved into meeting
a bunch of random kids
that only want a picture with me.
It doesn't feel good.
You were failed. We did not
do a good job last night.
You were set up very badly. All truth.
God.
And then, also, nobody
tells me who's important.
All of you said,
"Okay, you're done. Go back."
And I start going back and then
you're like, "Billie. Billie. Billie."
And I hear "Billie."
All I hear is "Billie."
So how am I supposed to know that
that's an important Billie? The fuck?
I think we're changing
how we're gonna do this--
All I hear is, "Billie. Billie. Billie."
Every second of my fucking life.
-Billie, it was a big, giant fail.
-But from every direction.
-Everywhere I go. "Billie!"
-It was a big fail.
-And then I turn around
and it's, like, the dude that runs,
like, whatever--
some huge magazine
who wants me on the cover.
I don't want anyone who knows
who I am and is any sort of fan,
or knows a fan, to see me
in any sort of awkward situation.
-Okay.
-Got it.
It's embarrassing
and I have to keep smiling,
and if I don't, then they hate me and
they think I'm horrible. That's not fair.
-Yeah.
-I agree.
So... no throwing her to the wolves.
Okay.
Sheesh.
Hello!
Billie!
-You don't know how much I appreciate you.
-I love you, dude. Come here.
-I love you so much.
-Let's have a hug. I love you.
-I love you so much!
-Oh, my gosh!
-Oh, my gosh.
-How you feeling tonight?
I love you so much!
-How you guys doin'? You're good?
-We're fine.
We love you!
Hello!
Oh, my God. I love you so much!
Okay. Drive her out of here.
Look at my tattoo! Billie, Billie!
Billie!
Billie, I love you!
You saved my life.
Billie, your music saved my life.
-I love you!
-I love you, Billie!
Billie, I love you. I love you so much.
Oh, my gosh, Billie!
Buona sera.
Ciao bella.
♪ Sleepless long nights ♪
♪ That is what my youth was for ♪
♪ Old teenage hopes
Are alive at your door ♪
♪ Left you with nothing
But they want some more ♪
♪ Oh, uh, oh ♪
♪ You're changing your heart ♪
♪ You know who you are ♪
♪ Sweetheart, bitter heart ♪
Immediately.
Dude, I sprained my ankle immediately.
That's so embarrassing.
It's so stupid because I'm, like,
choked up right now
because I'd rather not do a show
than do a crappy version for you.
Like, I just want to give you
a good show and, like, I can't.
Shit!
This is so trash.
This is literally a nightmare, for real.
I can't do this. I'm sorry, bro.
So embarrassing.
Bitch!
I can't even go on... I choked up.
I can't even talk.
It's so fucking dumb.
They'll take whatever you give them.
And they'll totally be on your side.
They're stoked that you're here.
And you've traveled so far.
You got this.
Just start "idontwannabeyouanymore"
as soon as you walk back on stage.
You don't have to sit there
and talk and choke up.
Just start the song. Yeah?
Ready?
-Let's do it.
-Okay.
Tear it up, boss.
Yeah.
Thank you, Milan. I love you a lot.
I'm sorry.
-You have to heal your ankle...
-Crazy.
...and exercise your ankle
and strengthen your body.
-Not today!
-Yeah, every day!
I gave you the exercises to do, but
you actually do have to do it every day.
And the days when you don't have a show,
you have to almost do more.
Because you have to work out.
We're trying to make it
so you don't get injured anymore.
We're trying to heal your body
so that you don't go on interviews
and say "My body's broken."
We're gonna heal your body.
My body is always gonna be broken.
Even if I heal it.
-No, it's not gonna be broken.
-It will have been broken a million times.
But it can be healed.
When something breaks
a bunch of times, it's broken.
But that's why you have
to strengthen yourself.
Even if you fix it,
it's still been broken.
You have to strengthen yourself.
I think I've got
the start of the James Bond song.
It is called "No Time to Die"
because, like, that's just how
you make an iconic song.
It's like, you just have it--
Yeah, yeah.
I had some ideas on the plane too.
-I think it's not a sad Sam Smith ballad.
-No.
I think it's, like,
a fucking angry-ass song.
-Anyway, I love you.
-I love you too!
Look at my ankle, bro. Crack!
Boom! Normal. Sad.
Happy. Sad. Happy. Sad.
We called Freddy in desperation,
and he came to Barcelona
and saved the day.
We didn't realize
that it was torn ligaments.
It was much more dire than we had thought.
Lie on your side.
Good. Off you go, up and down.
Relax.
That's it. Better.
♪ I should have known ♪
♪ I'd leave alone ♪
There you go.
Good. Try and hit me
in the head with your knee.
♪ Just goes to show ♪
♪ That the blood you bleed
Is just the blood you owe ♪
♪ We were a pair ♪
♪ But I saw you there ♪
-♪ Too much to bear ♪
-Let's swap sides.
♪ You were my life
But life is far away from fair ♪
♪ Was I stupid to love you? ♪
♪ Was I reckless to help? ♪
♪ Was it obvious to everybody else? ♪
♪ That I'd fallen for a lie? ♪
♪ You were never on my side ♪
♪ Fool me once, fool me twice ♪
♪ Are you death or paradise? ♪
♪ Now you'll never see me cry ♪
♪ There's just no time to die ♪
I say just, "It's no time to die"
at the end.
That works.
Sounds like a Bond song to me.
The greenroom will never be quiet enough.
So we're gonna just go sit on the bus.
♪ Was I stupid to love you? ♪
♪ Was I reckless to help? ♪
♪ Was it obvious to everybody else-- ♪
Oh, my God. I hate this.
-What's wrong with it?
-♪ Was it obvious to everybody else ♪
Ah, I hate this!
Billie, I don't want you to blow--
Why do people belt?
-It sound--
-Awful.
-It sounds great.
-It sounds stupid.
No, it sounds great.
You don't have to belt.
I'm gonna get made fun of by the Internet
when I do it.
No, you're not.
The Internet is going to be mean
if I do it.
I don't think so.
But I don't want you to hurt your voice
before a show.
-How's your voice feeling?
-Not good.
-Do you wanna stop?
-No.
-Should you stop?
Go again.
♪ You were never on my side ♪
♪ Fool me on-- ♪
Okay, well.
We have to send it in--
-I can try it.
-We have to send it in tonight. So...
-Tonight?
-Mm-hmm.
Like, be done for real, for real?
We don't have to send it in,
like, here's--
here's the final production,
final everything.
But we have to send them the song tonight.
Yep.
♪ Told you not to worry ♪
♪ But maybe that's a lie ♪
Ouch.
♪ Honey, what's your hurry? ♪
♪ Won't you stay inside? ♪
♪ Remember not to get too close to stars ♪
♪ They're never gonna give you
Love like ours ♪
♪ Where did you go?
I should know, but it's cold ♪
♪ And I don't wanna be lonely
So show me the way home ♪
♪ I can't lose another life ♪
♪ Hurry, I'm worried ♪
♪ The world's a little blurry ♪
♪ Or maybe it's my eyes ♪
-Thank you, Houston! We love you so much!
♪ Fool me once
Fool me twice ♪
♪ Are you death or paradise?
Now you'll nev-- ♪
-Okay.
-Great.
Can you believe we did a whole show today?
And also we wrote
a lot of this song today.
And also it's midnight, and also we're
recording. We really are millionaires.
That's not what that...
That, no-- That makes no sense at all.
It's just all true things.
"We really are millionaires."
We're so not.
We have millions of dollars,
but that does not make us millionaires.
Billie the millionaire.
-Millionaire.
-♪ She's dangerous, super bad ♪
♪ She's a gold digger ♪
Oh, my God.
Goodbye from the both of us. Mwah.
300,000 people watched that shit. Why?
You do cover any number of topics,
you know, that are difficult.
Whether it's, you know, depression,
anxiety. Very personal topics.
Why be so transparent?
I never decided to.
I never was, like, "I'm gonna talk about
this. And I'm gonna talk about this."
-Mm.
-I just talked about what I was feeling.
And talked about
why it was bad or why it was good
or why it was whatever.
And then it became this, like,
"Oh she's making a statement."
Which I actually love
because I didn't realize I was.
And now that I think about it, like,
I realize how many people aren't
talking about that kind of stuff
and why people are so, like,
shocked when you do talk about it.
I'm like, "Why is that so shocking?
Like, I'm telling you, like,
about how I am as a human.
Like, why is that weird?"
To be honest with you,
I didn't think
I would make it to this age.
There's one page in-- Ooh.
Damn it. Look at that.
Wow, I was in such a bad place. Whoa.
Found it.
There it is.
This page, it was kinda, like,
the peak, I would say.
I was, like, 14, 15.
I had razors hidden in places.
And I had Band-Aids hidden
in a little corner of my room.
And I always had Band-Aids on my wrists.
I was literally locking myself
in the bathroom
and making myself bleed
'cause I thought I deserved it, you know?
The full list
of 62nd Grammy nominations are here.
Hi, love.
Good morning.
It's like Christmas morning.
But no presents.
No presents.
This is kind of a present.
Do you wanna hear?
-Okay.
-Morning, Bill.
"Nominations. Record of the Year:
'Bad Guy.'
Album of the Year"--
What album would that be?
Pepper's a bozo.
"When We All Fall Asleep, Where Do We Go?
Song of the Year: 'Bad Guy'.
Best New Artist."
Why do you sound like that?
-"Best Pop Solo Performance..."
-'Cause she's your mom.
"...and Best Pop Vocal Album."
And Producer of the Year
would be your brother.
-Oh, he got it?
-Yeah.
Yay! He was so anxious about that.
Uh, hello,
I'm putting you on the speaker phone.
You can talk to your sister.
Eilish.
Guess what you did.
Did you see?
You gotted what you wanted.
Billie, congratulations on
being nominated for fucking everything.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-You too, Finneas.
-It's unreal.
-I wanna make you some food, Billie.
I love you.
♪ Taste me ♪
♪ The salty tears on my cheek ♪
♪ That's what a year-long headache ♪
♪ Does to you ♪
♪ I'm not okay
I feel so scattered ♪
♪ Don't say I'm all that matters ♪
♪ Leave me ♪
♪ Déjà vu ♪
♪ If you need me ♪
♪ Wanna see me ♪
♪ Better hurry ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm leavin' soon ♪
I'm nominated for six Grammys,
and I have my dream car.
And Finneas has his dream car.
And it's raining.
And I have my pooch doggy in the car.
I had doughnuts last night.
I'm not in a relationship,
thank the lords.
My relationship with my family is good.
I am pretty. Somewhat.
I am famous... ...as fuck.
Life is good.
Who got nominated for a Grammy today?
Me and Finneas.
-Billie and Finneas.
-I am nominated for six Grammys,
and we still are in the same
stupid little backyard.
But that's nice, that's a nice thing.
I know, I'm joking. I think it's cute.
Ahhh.
-Butterflies...
-Yeah.
-All good.
-You got this.
An incredible last year for you.
What does it mean to be at the Grammys,
you grew up not far from here,
walking down this carpet
going into the Staples Center tonight?
It's your first Grammys,
and you have six nominations.
Billie, happy birthday.
-It's my birthday, I'm 18.
-Happy birthday.
And the Grammy goes to...
"Bad Guy," by Billie Eilish.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
So, there's
an artist called Billie Eilish.
She recently came out with an album
that is completely satanic.
And the Grammy goes to...
Billie Eilish!
Oh, gee.
Huh? Whoo!
Thank you. Ayayay.
Two.
Director, Billie Eilish.
Look at that.
Put your feet down flat.
Yeah, like, let it come onto your foot.
Yes!
And the Grammy goes to...
Billie Eilish!
Let's go.
I-- I love you. Thank you for this.
Yeah!
Whoa, okay.
And the Grammy goes to...
"Bad Guy," Billie Eilish.
-Thank you.
Bye!
We made this album in a bedroom
at our house that we grew up in.
And it was mastered
in somebody's living room,
so it's really like anything is possible.
Best New Artist,
Album of the Year, Song of the Year,
Record of the Year, Pop Vocal Album,
Producer of the Year.
If the instruments weren't in the house
that you guys were growing up in,
would you have still made music?
I don't know. Our parents were really good
about, um, listening to what we wanted
and never forcing anything on us.
I think we grew up in such a way
that made us feel like we could
just do and be whatever we wanted.
They just supported it.
Hey, Rob! There he is.
Answer it.
Oh, my--
Congrats.
-Thank you!
-How you feeling?
I'm good.
I'm good. How are you?
Wasn't it amazing? How did it feel?
Everything you could've imagined or what?
Yes, completely. I can't believe it.
It's insane.
That's awesome.
I'm so proud-- I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
You've been working hard for this.
Thanks to you.
Stop it.
How are you? Are you good?
I'm really good, yeah.
Where's your brother, by the way?
-Finneas?
-I have no pants on.
-But it's Justin Bieber.
Quicker, quicker.
Hey, Justin.
Hey, man. Congrats, bro.
Thank you. That is so nice of you.
All those long nights
writing those songs, bro.
And you're at the freaking Grammys
crushing it.
All right,
I don't wanna, you know...
I want you guys to go enjoy yourselves.
We will. I'm-- This is crazy. Ayayay.
Thank you for calling me. I love you.
Love you too. Bye.
Bye!
Oh!
-♪ I've never... ♪
-♪ Fallen from quite this high ♪
♪ Fallin' into your ocean eyes ♪
♪ Those ocean eyes ♪
Whoo!
Thanks. Bye. See you next year.
Modify by Blue-Bird™
(https://subscene.com/u/1191276)
Sync & corrections by Blue-Bird™